Guide to the Screamers collection, circa 1963-1981.
Screamers collection,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Screamers collection, circa 1963-1981.
8126
3.5 cubic feet.
Fliers, newspapers, magazines, correspondence, manuscripts, and photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes original art, photographs and fliers, a 1977 fan club application, press kits, press releases, files of handwritten lyrics, letters, press clippings and magazines, publicity and business plans, guest lists, fan club mailing lists, and other business records and correspondence
The Screamers were an American punk rock group formed in 1975 that participated in the first wave Los Angeles, California punk scene. Often categorized as electropunk, their sound included a synthesizer (ARP Odyssey) and electric piano (Fender Rhodes). Other punk musicians and bands have cited the Screamers as a key influence. The group never released an official recording of any kind, although several bootleg recordings of rehearsals or live performances have since appeared; they have been called one of the great unrecorded groups in rock history. Artist Gary Panter's logo for the band, a stylized cartoon of a screaming head with spiked hair, became one of the most recognizable images to emerge from punk rock.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes original art, photographs and fliers, a 1977 fan club application, press kits, press releases, files of handwritten lyrics, letters, press clippings and magazines, including TOLO, the Franklin High School (Seattle, WA) Newsletter with articles authored by Tommy Tibbits (Gear), a notebook that belonged to Tomata du Plenty (1978), touring, publicity and business plans, guest lists, fan club mailing lists, plans to release a debut album in video form, and other business records and correspondence
Subjects:
Gender identity.; Punk rock music.; Punk culture.; Punk rock musicians.; Punk culture -- Los Angeles.; Punk rock musicians -- Los Angeles.; The Screamers (Musical group).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Business records
Series II. NY Emmaus House
Series III. Lyric sheets and booklets
Series IV. Photographs, original art, and recordings
Series V. Posters and fliers
Series VI. Publicity and press materials
CONTAINER LIST
- Business records, 1967-1980
  - Contracts, financial and legal materials, 1977-1979
    - Screamers Contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Contains various contracts, m/s and typed, for The Screamers shows, appearances, tapes, etc.
    - Taxes Finance Performance, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Contains various documentations of payments for shows, most by hand, on backs of Xeroxed fliers, calendars, etc.
    - Correspondence from Tommy Gear to television stations and zines, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Concerning unauthorized use of Screamers video footage and reprinting of confidential letters
    - Q and A about Trademarks booklet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Various business cards for lawyers, Undated; Stapled to sheet of paper (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Letter from Law Offices of Martin Gilbert, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ficticious Business Name Statement, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Form filled out by Tommy Tibbits, with receipt
    - Proof of Publication form for The Screamers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Small Business Office letter, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Motion Picture Release Forms, 1977; 4 copies; Signed. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Screamers Misc., 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Contains handwritten PR planning, notes on performance, t-shirt printing, tax documents, etc.
  - Phone numbers, tour expenses, recording schedules and costs, 1978; Blue notebook. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Belonged to Tomata
  - Business Correspondence, 1970-1980
    - Barney Wood and Becky Burns (B and B) Trips, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Envelope containing Tommy Gear’s letters to and from Barney Wood and Becky Burns (B and B)
    - Handmade birthday card/zine for Melba Toast (Tommy Gear) from Sherree and Francine, 1970-1979; Includes pins and photographs collaged into card. In Pee-Chee Portfolio (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Early CBGB and Ramones photos.
    - Business Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Envelope containing various receipts, letters from court, library collection notices for Tommy Gear, tax returns and tax correspondence
    - Envelope addressed to Tommy Gear from San Gabriel Valley Tribune, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Handwritten from article author Russell Gollard. Contains 2 copies of SGV Tribune Weekender, 8/4/78 (pg. 12-13, ‘Punk’ article, quotes from Tomata and Tommy Gear)
  - Fan Club Materials, 1977-1979
    - Birthday Greetings, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Page for fan club announcing Tommy Gear’s birthday
    - Quotes to Lace around Sheila’s Interview, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Pulled quotes for interview
    - Summer Foods to Enjoy in Your Garden, Undated; Typed recipe with collaged images (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Tommy Gear Questionnaire, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Tomato Du Plenty Questionnaire, Undated; 2 pages; Typed on blue paper (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - KK Kwestionarre, Undated; 2 pages; Typed on blue paper (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Paul Roessler Questionnaire, Undated; 2 pages; Typed on blue paper (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Screamers Fans Unite!!, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Membership sign up for Fan Club
    - We haven’t forgotten you, 1979-02-02; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Letter to members of Screamers Fan Club.
    - We haven’t forgotten you, 1979-02-02 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Letter to members of Screamers Fan Club with Gary Panter logo in corner. One copy original, one Xeroxed
    - Thanks for waiting so long, 1979; 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Letter from Screamers fan club.
    - Handwritten notes about pricing of Screamers T shirts, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Various pages from Screamers fanzine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Photocopies.
    - Savings passbook for Screamers Fan Club bank account, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Disc Tech Tearsheet Article, 1979-07; Love, John; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 2)
      From TWA Ambassador.
    - Screamers - amount of expenses and payouts, 1977; Yellow envelope containing 3 receipts (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Screamers Fan Club letter, 1979-03-02 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - New Clues to Causes of Violence, Undated; Black and white (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Screamers Fan Club Zine #2. 5 pg.
    - Crewlist Screamers, 1979-07; 2 copies; Typed (Box 1, Folder 3)
      List of Screamers personnel for a show at the Roxy.
    - Screamers Guestlist, 1979-07-21; Typed (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Screamers Guestlist, 1979-07-20; Typed (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Screamers Guestlist, 1979-07-19; Typed (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Screamers Best, 1978-12 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Fan club mailer.
    - Screamers Fan Club Membership form No. 2, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Featuring Eric Blum’s photograph of the band (Membership for $4 fee).
      Offset lithographs.
    - Screamers Fans Unite, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      First Screamers Fan Club application. Photo by Herb Wrede. Xerox
    - Screamers Fan Club application, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Photo by Tom Griswold. Not well circulated
    - Screamers Best, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Page from Screamer’s fan club mailing signed “Hiya! - Tomata” by Tomata du Plenty, addressed to Jon Savage
    - Rio’s Questionnaire with Tomata, 1977-01; Typed (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Tomasino Questionnaire, 1970-1979; 7 pages; Holiday images on reverse, questions regarding fame and future plans (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Tomata’s Questionnaire on G. Bugatti, 1977; Typed, photo collage on reverse (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Quiz and Interview with "Gianni Bugatti", 1976-12; Handwritten (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Screamers Fan Club Application flier, 1970-1979; Collaged with Ken Banks photograph and text below (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - “Screamers Fans Unite!!” Fan Club Membership form No. 1, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      (Membership for a $2 fee) featuring Eric Blum’s photograph of the band
  - 123 Rhapsody film, 1978-1979
    - The 123 Rhapsody Summary, 1979; Daalder, R.; Illustrated and typed. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Treatment for film.
    - Modern Props, Undated; Color and black and white (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Photographs of sets and props, with blue back page with information of the company
    - An Introduction to Rhapsody Entertainments and the Screamers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Binder containing Press Kit and correspondence concerning the press kit
    - Typed list of crew members with contact information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Renee Daalder resume packet, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The 1,2,3 Rhapsody, 1978; Daalder, Rene (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Extended treatment for film
  - Mailings, 1977-1979
    - Rolodex cards for NYC labels, press, television, radio, etc., Undated; 42 cards (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Contact information for Tomata du Plenty and Tommy Gear, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      As well as other numbers, list of food on back. Page from notebook
    - Press phone numbers for LA, CA, Undated; Handwritten list in pencil and ink. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Note about playing a show w/ Suicide and the B-52s, Undated; White paper/blue ink (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Message slips for Tommy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Regarding press, shows, radio, etc.
    - Various scrap papers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      With addresses, numbers, contact info and other small notes, m/s.
    - Ken Banks photograph, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Glossy ad with phone number.
    - List of phone numbers, Undated; Handwritten on white pape (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Includes names, press, publications
    - List of NY publication addresses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Screamers Dates, 1977-05-1979-09; 2 pg. yellow paper. Typed. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - To Be Sent Fan Club Material, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Typed list of names and addresses (names includes Jerry of Devo)
    - LA photographers, Undated; Typed list (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - ‘LA Radio’ stations, Undated; Typed list (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Screamers mailing list, Undated; 3 pages (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Includes names, labels, press (list of who was sent a copy of the Screamers release)
    - Red scrap paper with hand written directions, Undated; Signed on verso, “Tomata or David” (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Fan Club Mailing Lists, Undated; Typed with handwritten updates. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Booklet of music publication addresses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - San Diego publicity addresses: radio and TV, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - List of phone numbers, Undated; Handwritten in black marker, written on back of flyer for Whisky, LA, CA. shows 4/13-15/78 (G. Panter, M. Gira (SWANS), C. Weirdo) (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ohio Ohio Akron, Ohio, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Lists of addresses (addresses for Pirate’s Cove, DEVO: Bob and Mark, press, record stores, radio and television.)
    - Baltimore Baltimore Baltimore, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Copies of addresses for record stores, radio, press and television
    - East Coast: Conn, Ohio, Vermont, Chicago, Penn, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Page of Fan Club addresses
    - Old Address Lists, Undated; Typed (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Mailing lists for New York, Philadelphia, Toronto, Montreal, Connecticut, Pennsylvania, Ohio, Vermont, Chicago, Pittsburgh, Baltimore, Boston (New York list contains names such as Lou Reed, Lux and Ivy (The Cramps), Ramones, Richard Hell, Gene Simmons, Sylvain, Richard Lloyd, Alan Vega, Sabel Starr, Debbie Harry and Chris Stein, Lenny Kaye, Lydia Lunch, Cheetah Chrome, Danny Fields)
  - Record Companies, Undated
    - Record company names and contact information, Undated; Handwritten (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Various notes on scraps of paper
    - “We passed on Screamers, I gave it to SIRE to evaluate, they also passed - nothing new.”, Undated; Handwritten note on Warner Brothers Records stationary from Roberta Peterson (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Letter from Stan Cornyn, 1978; Typed (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Executive Vice President of Warner Brothers Records, officially passing on the Screamers.
- NY Emmaus House, 1967-1968
  - Pamphlet for Emmaus House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    San Francisco, California
  - Going on at Emmaus NYC, 1968-02-1968-06 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Calendar of events flyer
  - Community News Notes Newsletter, Emmaus House, 1968-06-01 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gregory Baum's nationally syndicated column, 1968-01-05 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Article on Emmaus House
  - NY Times, 1968-01-07; Hofman, Paul (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Newsweek, 1967-11-27 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Unity Trends, Vol. 1, No. 6, 1968-02-01 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Emmaus pamphlet
  - The Freedom Movement in Churches, 1967; 4 pages; Typed (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Emmaus House Guidelines and Manifesto. Outlines current and future plans for house
  - Toward A Secular Understanding of the Ecumenical?, 1967; Van Den Heuvel, Albert H.; 7 pages; Typed (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Excerpts from article “the Humiliation of the Church”
  - Emmaus House Newsletter, 1968-05 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Letter from David Kirk, 1968-05; Typed (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Coordinator of Emmaus House.
  - ‘Manifesto of Emmaus’: our first editorial: the Bread is Rising, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Four Meditations, Undated; Strom, Hester G.; Typed (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Litany for the Underground, 1 and 2, Undated; Castle, Robert W., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Lyric sheets and booklets, 1977-1979
  - The Damned Disciples Song Book, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Lyric booklet for the Damned albums ‘Stretcher Case’ and ‘Sick of Being Sick’
  - I Wanna Be Your Dog, No. 7, 1977-11 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Inside has adds for Sex Pistols ‘Nevermind the Bollocks’ and Elvis Costello’s ‘My Aim is True’
  - Manuscript Lyrics for 122 Hours of Fear, Eva Braun, Peer Pressure, Last Four Digits, A Better World Begins With Me, Magazine Love, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    With excerpts of lyrics from Punish or Be Damned, If I Can’t Have What I Want I Don’t Want Anything, The Age of Unreason
  - Why the World, Nervous, (Short), Violent World, Mensch, She Frightens, I Wanna Hurt, I Go For You, Friends, Vertigo, Punisher Be Damned, For Old Times Sake, 1977-1979; Typed and handwritten notes in pencil (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Lyric Booklet
  - For Old Time’s Sake, Undated; 3 pages; Typed (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - For Old Time’s Sake, 1977-1979; 4 pages; Typed with handwritten notes and interactions for tape and recording (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - I Wanna Hurt, Undated; Gear, Tommy; Typed, stapled (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sheila/ Lyrics, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Sheila Edwards Birth Certificate, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Strange Romance, 1979; Handwritten lyrics (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Immortality of Love, 1979; Handwritten lyrics (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Imortality of Love, 1979; Handwritten notes, lyrics, shorthand (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Who’s Deciding, 1979; Typed lyrics (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Who’s Deciding, 1979; Handwritten lyrics (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - RipCord, 1979; Handwritten lyrics in pencil, (w/ notes on song structure and music) (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - A Strange Romance, 1979; Handwritten lyrics in pencil (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - RipCord, 1979; Handwritten lyrics, Xeroxed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Who’s Deciding, 1979; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lyrics (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - the Scream, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Why the World, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - (It) Makes Me Nervous, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - I am A Mensch, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - She Frightens, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - I Wanna Hurt, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Includes lyrics and notes
    - I Go For You, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Friends Right Now, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Vertigo(Let’s Go—), Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Punish or Be Damned, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - For Old Time’s Sake, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Screamers Lyrics and Music (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Eva Braun, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Punish or Be Damned, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics and stage notes
    - Friends Right Now, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics and notes
    - Friends Right Now, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Partial lyric sheet
    - I am A Mensch!, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics, stage notes and direction, banter instructions, (duct tape top of page, reverse side ‘Bass Prog’ notes)
    - Why the World, Undated; Typed lyrics and handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - the Scream, Undated; Typed lyrics and handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - She Frightens, Undated; Typed lyrics and handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes key changes, lyric additions and adlibs
    - She Frightens, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes stage/song notes (stapled ‘Female Supplement’)
    - She Frightens, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes updated female notes and direction
    - Friends Right Now, Undated; Typed lyrics and handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - the Scream, Undated; Typed lyrics and handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes key changes, updated lyrics and ad-libs
    - possible unreleased/unrecorded Screamers song, Undated; Handwritten lyrics on notebook paper (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Peer Pressure, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Partial lyrics
    - Vertigo, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Don’t Pay the Whore, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Anything, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Mater Dolores, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - G.O, Guy, 1977; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - I’m Going Steady with Twiggy, 1976; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Better World, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - I Wanna Hurt, Undated; Gear, Tommy; Typed, stapled (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Violent World, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Penelope and Tomata (unreleased), Undated; Typed lyrics, ‘Penelope and Tomata’ written on bottom. Xerox (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Unreleased
    - Why the World (viola), Nervous (violin), Violent World, I Am A Mensch, She Frightens (viola), I Want to Hurt (w/ vocal cues and piano notes), Friends (viola), Vertigo, Pun- ish, 122 Hours, Old Tyme’s Sake, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Sheet music
    - Screamers Songs - Basic tracks/ Rough takes, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      List of rough takes; Vertigo, Punish, Peer Pressure, Frightens, I Wanna Hurt, BCM, He Girlin…, IZZ, Better World, Violent World
    - When the Dance Begins, That’s When Strangers Meet (unreleased), Undated; Typed with handwritten notes (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics for unreleased Screamers song. Black pen, stained paper
    - Why the World, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      5 different versions
    - Where the Music Should Go, Undated; Typed large format (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Includes recording notes, lines, arrangements and cues. Reads like a script for a solo performance, with all parts for Tomata.
    - I AM A Mensch!, Undated; Typed large format (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics, vocal cues, interlude and intermezzo for notations.
    - Vertigo, Undated; 3 pages; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Different intro, verses and chorus locations, additional lyrics
    - Why the World, Nervous, Violent World, I AM A Mensch, She Frightens, I Wanna Hurt, I Go For You, Friends, Vertigo, Punish or Be Damned, For Old Time’s Sake, Undated; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics booklet
    - I Wanna Hurt, 1979; Gear, Tommy; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics and cover sheet
    - Peer Pressure, 1979; Typed (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics (incomplete)
    - the Girl in the Car with the Glasses On, Vertigo, Peer Pressure, She Frightens, Hurt, Undated; On typewriter paper (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Lyrics for the songs, Hurt is formerly ‘I Wanna Hurt’ by T.G.
- Photographs, original art, and recordings, 1977-2004
  - Photographs, 1977-1979
    - Screamers black and white press photograph, 1977-04-09; Stern, Jenny (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Photograph by Jenny Stern (aka Jenny Lens), marked and stamped
    - Black and White Screamers press photographs, 1978; Blum, Eric (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Five unique images from the same photo shoot
      Gelatin silver prints..
    - Tommy Gear photograph, 1978; Hand painted and colored (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Unknown photographer
    - Unknown subject, Undated; Color photograph (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tommy Gear and KK in San Francisco, 1979; Ray, Ruby; Black and White Photograph (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Search and Destroy stamp on back
    - Screamers backstage at Mabuhay Gardens, 1978; Zie, Kamera; Black and White Photograph (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tomata du Plenty dancing on stage at Mabuhay Gardens, 1978; Zie, Kamera; Black and White Photograph (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Tomata du Plenty performing on stage at Mabuhay Gardens, 1978; Zie, Kamera; Black and White Photograph (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Screamers performing on stage at Mabuhay Gardens, 1977; Zie, Kamera; Black and White Photograph (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Black and White photograph of Tomata and KK, 1977-1979; Pin holes in corners of print (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Gelatin silver prints.
    - Screamers performing live, 1977-1979; Hoffman, Jill; Color photograph (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Print by Jill Hoffman/Target
  - Original art, 1979
    - Screamers, 1979; Original mechanical in color by Gary Panter 1979, signed recto by artist on mount, initialed in image. (Box 7)
    - Tomata du Plenty, Undated; Original art [stenciled spray paint on board] in black and white and color, initialed lower right recto “TdP” by Tomata du Plenty. (Box 7)
    - Tomata du Plenty, Undated; Original art [stenciled spray paint on board] in black and white and color, initialed lower right recto “TdP” by Tomata du Plenty. (Box 7)
  - Recordings, 2001-2004
    - In a Better World, 2001; CD-3530 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      CD: Screamers Live at the Whisky a Go-Go 1/6-7/78, Live at the Roxy 5/17-19-79, Demos. Released on ExtraVertigo Recordings and Xeroid Records, ltd. ed #93/250
    - Screamers Live in San Francisco, CA. 9/2/78, 2004; DVD-2386 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      DVD, released by Target Video Presents Live and MVD
- Posters and fliers, 1974-1979
  - Screamers, Whiskey and One Show Nitely, 1970-1979; Graph paper folded containing magazine cut out letters used to create posters and prints. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Screamers shows @ Whisky in Los Angeles
    Los Angeles, California
  - Special SPIT Previews at Hilly’s CBGB Tavern, 1974-09-21-1974-09-22; Gorilla Rose, Tomata duPlenty and Co.; Questionnaire on verso (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Photo by Sheyla.
    New York, New York
  - Tupperwares at the Odd Fellows Temple, 1976-05-01; With red marker annotations (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Seattle, Washington
  - Screamers (Tomata and KK), Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Screamers at Starwood, 1977-07-04- (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Screamers with Street Punks at Mabuhay Gardens, 1977-07-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Screamers with Dead Beats at Mabuhay Gardens, 1977-12-18-1978-12-19 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ticket for Slash presents Weirdos and Screamers at The Masque, 1977-12-16 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Hollywood, CA
  - Screamers at Mabuhay Gardens, 1977-07-28-1977-07-29 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Signed by Tomata, KK, and David Brown. Flier with photograph taken by Fayette
  - Screamers, X, Alley Cats, and Flesh Eaters at Marquee West, 1978-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    With photographs.
  - Screamers, X, Alley Cats, and Flesh Eaters at Marquee West, 1978-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    With Gary Panter logo